Syracuse University Publications in Continuing Education (SUPCE) Records
Syracuse University Publications in Continuing Education (SUPCE) Records
- Publications
  - Notes and Essays in Continuing Education for Adults series (NES)
    - NES43 Perspective on Automation: Three Talks to Educators (Theobald, Robert; Johnston, John W. C.; Weinberg, Jack), 1964 (Box 14)
    - NES44 Growing Time (DeCrow, Roger, editor), 1964 (Box 14)
    - NES45 Meaning and Metaphor (Goldberg, Maxwell H.), 1965 (Box 14)
    - NES46 A Live Option: Potentials for the Evening College (Haygood, Kenneth, editor) (Box 14)
    - NES47 A Turning to Take Next: Alternative Goals in the Education of Woman (Goldman, Freda H.), 1965 (Box 14)
    - NES48 Education in the Peace Corps: Evolving Concepts of Volunteer Training (Pagano, Jules), 1965 (Box 14)
    - NES49 Toward a Homeodynamic Society (Blakely, R. J.), 1965 (Box 14)
    - NES50 Institutional Backgrounds of Adult Education: Dynamics of change in the Modern University (Ingham, R. J., editor) (Box 14)
    - NES51 Oakland Papers: Symposium on Social Change and Educational Continuity (Whipple, James B. and Woditsch, Gary A., editors), 1966 (Box 14)
    - NES52 Speaking for Myself: A Humanist Approach to Adult Education for a Technical Age (Deinum, Andries), 1966 (Box 14)
    - NES53 Political Backgrounds of Adult Education: The University in Urban Society (Cummings, Thomas, editor), 1967 (Box 14)
    - NES54 The Continuing Task: Reflections on Purpose in Higher Continuing Education (Houle, Cyril O.; Blackwell, Gordon W.; Kallen, Horace M.; Whipple, James B.), 1967 (Box 14)
    - NES55 A Critical Balance: History of CSLEA (Whipple, James B.), 1967 (Box 14)
    - NES56 On Behalf of Adult Education: A Historical Examination of the Supporting Literature (Cotton, Webster E.), 1958 (Box 14)
    - NES57 Anthropological Background of Adult Education (Tax, Sol; Diamond, Stanley; Rainwater, Lee; Mangin, William; Bharati, Ahehananda), 1968 (Box 14)
    - NES58 Of Messages and Media: Teaching and Learning by Public Television (Alter, Henry C.), 1968 (Box 14)
    - NES59 The System of Adult Education in Yugoslavia (Savicevic, Dusan M.), 1968 (Box 14)
      See also Drafts, notes and galleys: NES59 The System of Adult Education in Yugoslavia
    - NES60 Liberal Education Reconsidered: Reflections on Continuing Education for Contemporary Man (Whipple, James B.; Goldman, Freda H.; Haygood, Kenneth Siegle, Peter), 1960 (Box 14)
      See also Drafts, notes and galleys: NES60 Liberal Education Reconsidered: Reflections on Continuing Education for Contemporary Man
    - NES61 Aim: From Concept to Reality (Wedemeyer, Charles A. Najem, Robert E.), 1969 (Box 14)
      See also Drafts, notes and galleys: NES61 Aim: From Concept to Reality
    - NES62 Dilemmas of American Policy: Crucial Issues in Contemporary Society (Cook, Samuel Dubois; Stern, George G.; Green, Thomas F.; Weiner, Anthony J.), 1969 (Box 14)
      See also Drafts, notes and galleys: NES62 Dilemmas of American Policy: Crucial Issues in Contemporary Society
    - NES63 Knowledge is Power to Control Power (Blakely, Robert and Lappin, I.), 1969 (Box 14)
      See also Drafts, notes and galleys: NES63 Knowledge is Power to Control Power
    - NES64 The University and Community Service (Whipple, James B. and Chertow, Doris), 1970 (Box 14)
      See also Drafts, notes and galleys: NES64 The University and Community Service
    - NES65 Essays on New Careers: Social Implications for Adult Educators (Riessman, Frank; Rosen, Sumner M.; Featherstone, Joseph; Gartner, Alan), 1970 (Box 14)
      See also Drafts, notes and galleys: NES65 Essays on New Careers: Social Implications for Adult Educators
    - NES66 Essays on the Future of Continuing Education Worldwide (Ziegler, Warren), 1970 (Box 14)
      See also Drafts, notes and galleys: NES66 Essays on the Future of Continuing Education Worldwide
    - NES67 Toward the Educative Society (Charters, Alexander N.), 1971 (Box 14)
    - NES68 Sensitivity Training: Processes, Problems and Applications (Blumberg, Arthur), 1971 (Box 14)
    - NES69 Ends and Means: The National Conference on Continuing Education in Nursing (McHenry, Ruth W.), 1971 (Box 14)
      See also Drafts, notes and galleys: NES69 Ends and Means: The National Conference on Continuing Education in Nursing
    - NES70 Residential Continuing Education (Houle, Cyril O.), 1971 (Box 14)
      See also Drafts, notes and galleys: NES70 Residential Continuing Education
    - NES71 Selected Concepts from Educational Psychology and Adult Education for Extension and Continuing Educators (Leagans, J. Paul; Copeland, Harlan G.; Kaiser, Gertrude E.), 1971 (Box 14)
      See also Drafts, notes and galleys: NES71 Selected Concepts from Educational Psychology and Adult Education for Extension and Continuing Educators
    - NES72 International Seminar on Publications in Continuing Education (Charters, Alexander N. and Rivera, William M.), 1972 (Box 14)
  - Occasional Papers (CSLEA) series (OCP)
    - OCP1 Adult Education Programming Form and Function (Tuskegee Institute), 1960 (Box 14)
    - OCP2 National Trends in Higher Adult Education (Liveright, A. A.), 1960 (Box 14)
    - OCP3 Liberal Education for Community Clubs (Rhode, William E.), 1960 (Box 14)
    - OCP4 Liberal Orientations for Vocational Teaching (Miller, Harry L.), 1963 (Box 14)
    - OCP5 Adults That Grew in Brooklyn and Some That Didn't (Stern, Bernard H.), 1963 (Box 14)
    - OCP6 [MISSING] We Need a Philosophy (Diekhoff, John S.), 1963 (Box 14)
    - OCP7 New Eyes for Old: The Quest for Education (McKenna, Richard), 1963 (Box 14)
    - OCP8 The Human Enterprise (Rodney, Robert M.), 1964 (Box 14)
    - OCP9 Promoting High Standards of Professional Excellence (Horn, Francis H.), 1964 (Box 14)
    - OCP10 Inter-Association Cooperation Reconsidered (Spengler, Edwin H.; McMahon, Ernest E.; Winters, Clifford), 1965 (Box 15)
    - OCP11 The Case Against the Adult Dropout (Sheats, Paul), 1965 (Box 15)
    - OCP12 Significant Developments in Continuing Higher Education (Liveright, A. A. and Goldman, Freda H.), 1965 (Box 15)
    - OCP13 Purposes of the Evening College: Reflections in 1953 (Houle, Cyril O.; Blackwell, Gordon W.; Kallen, Horace M.; McGrath, Earl J.), 1967 (Box 15)
    - OCP14 Participation of Adults in Education: A Force-Field Analysis (Miller, Harry L.), 1967 (Box 15)
    - OCP15 Daytime School for Adults: A New Program Dimensions at University (Gordon, Morton), 1967 (Box 15)
    - OCP16 The College and Its Community: A Conference on Purpose and Direction in the Education of Adults (papers presented at University of Wisconsin by personnel from southern Negro colleges and northern universities), 1968 (Box 15)
    - OCP17 Toward a National Center for Higher Continuing Education (Hudson, Robert B.), 1968 (Box 15)
    - OCP18 The Mass Media in Adult Education (Ohliger, John), 1968 (Box 15)
    - OCP19 Accent on Adults: The Small College Program at Brooklyn (Jacobson, Myrtle S. and Offenbacher, Deborah I.), 1970 (Box 15)
      See also Drafts, notes and galleys: OCP19 Accent on Adults: The Small College Program at Brooklyn
    - OCP20 Faculty Perceptions of Continuing Education at Syracuse University (Porter, Lee), 1970 (Box 15)
      See also Drafts, notes and galleys: OCP20 Faculty Perceptions of Continuing Education at Syracuse University
    - OCP21 Community Service and Continuing Education (Whipple, James B.), 1970 (Box 15)
      See also Drafts, notes and galleys: OCP21 Community Service and Continuing Education
    - OCP22 Adult Education and the Disadvantaged Adult (Anderson, Darrel and Niemi, John), 1970 (Box 15)
      See also Drafts, notes and galleys: OCP22 Adult Education and the Disadvantaged Adult
    - OCP23 The New Environment: Questions for Adult Educators (Blakely, R. J.), 1971 (Box 15)
    - OCP24 Lifelong Learning or Lifelong Schooling: A Tentative View of the Ideas of Ivan Illich (Ohliger, John and McCarthy, C.), 1971 (Box 15)
      See also Drafts, notes and galleys: OCP24 Lifelong Learning or Lifelong Schooling: A Tentative View of the Ideas of Ivan Illich
    - OCP25 The Learning Force: A More Comprehensive Framework for Educational Policy (Moses, Stanley), 1971 (Box 15)
      See also Drafts, notes and galleys: OCP25 The Learning Force: A More Comprehensive Framework for Educational Policy
    - OCP26 Real Estate Tax Exemption for Continuing Education Programs (Charters, Alexander N.), 1972 (Box 15)
    - OCP27 The Hill and the Valley: The Story of University College Through 1964 (Charters, Alexander N.), 1972 (Box 15)
    - OCP28 Response to Need: A Case Study of Adult Education Graduate Program Development in the Southeast (Kozoll, C.), 1972 (Box 15)
    - OCP29 Agenda for Comparative Studies in Adult Education: International Expert Meeting Report form the International Expert Meeting, 1972 (Box 15)
    - OCP30 Toward Gog and Magog, or, A Critical Review of the Literature of Adult Group Discussion (Osinski, F.; Ohliger, John; McCarthy, C.), 1972 (Box 15)
    - OCP31 Historical and Cultural Influence Upon the Development of Residential Centers for Continuing Education (Jessup, F.), 1972 (Box 15)
    - OCP32 Paul Freire: A Revolutionary Dilemma for the Adult Educator (Grabowski, Stanley, editor), 1972 (Box 15)
    - OCP33 The Challenge of Modern Church-Public Relations (Reagan, M., editor, and Chertow, Doris), 1972 (Box 15)
    - OCP34 Consumer Education Programming in Continuing Education (Charters, Margaret), 1973 (Box 15)
    - OCP35 Conceptual Learning: Mollusks to Adult Education (Carlson, R.), 1973 (Box 15)
    - OCP36 Toward a Working Philosophy of Adult Education (Apps, J.), 1973 (Box 15)
    - OCP37 Adult Education in Church and Synagogue (Long, H.), 1973 (Box 15)
    - OCP38 Evaluating the Attainment of Objectives in Adult Education: Process, Properties, Problems, Prospects (Steele, Sara M. and Brack, Robert E.), 1973 (Box 15)
    - OCP39 Educational Television in Its Cultural and Public Affairs Dimension: A Selected Literature Review of Public Television as an Issue in Adult Education (Carlson, Robert A.), 1973 (Box 15)
    - OCP40 The Use of Instructional Television in Adult Education (Blakely, R. J.), 1974 (Box 15)
    - OCP41 The Syracuse Black Community (Sacks, Seymour and Andrew, Ralph), 1974 (Box 15)
    - OCP42 Development, Demonstration and Dissemination: Case Studies of Selected Special Projects in Basic Education (Beder, Harold W. and Darkenwald, Gordon G.), 1974 (Box 15)
    - OCP43 The University Council on Education for Public Responsibility, 1961-1965 (Davis, Granville D.), 1975 (Box 15)
    - OCP44 Comparative Studies in Adult Education: An Anthology (Bennet, Clif, editor; Kidd, J. Roby; Kulich, Jindra), 1975 (Box 15)
    - OCP45 Continuing Education of Adults in Colonial America (Long, Huey B.), 1976 (Box 15)
    - OCP46 Training Teachers of Adults: Models and Innovative Programs (Grabowski, Stanley), 1976 (Box 15)
    - OCP47 Adults in Transition, 1965 (Box 15)
    - OCP48 Understanding Group Behavior (Miller, Harry L.), 1953 (Box 15)
    - OCP49 CSLEA Newsletter Continuing Education for Adults, July 1961-May 1968 (Box 15)
    - OCP50 How Much Does Adult Experience Count (Stearn, Bernard H.), 1955 (Box 15)
    - OCP51 A Turning to Take Next (Goldman, Freda H.) (Box 15)
    - OCP52 Invitation to Literature: Discussion Guide (Smith, Russell F. W.), 1953 (Box 15)
    - OCP53 Our Modern Art, the Movies (Callenbach, Ernest), 1955 (Box 15)
    - OCP54 Scientists at Work (Sayvetz, Aaron), 1954 (Box 15)
    - OCP55 Understanding Group Behavior (Miller, Harry L.), 1953 (Box 15)
    - OCP56 Leading Group Discussion, Part I, II, III (Miller/Berger); Supplementary Readings (CSLEA); Discussion Guide (CSLEA); Training Guide (CSLEA), 1954; 1955; 2 folders (Box 15)
    - OCP57 Folder of Newsletters (CSLEA) (Box 15)
    - OCP58 [MISSING]
    - OCP59 The Contributions of Alexander N. Charters to the Field of Adult Education (Siddiqui, Dilnawaz) (Box 15)
  - Single publications (PRE)
    - PRE1 New Directions for Adult Education: Introduction (Charters, Alexander N.), 1958 (Box 15)
    - PRE2 [MISSING] Adult Education Procedures, Methods and Techniques: A Classified and Annotated Bibliography 1953-1963 (Aker, George), 1965 (Box 15)
    - PRE3 Leading Group Discussions: A Discussion Guide, 1969 (Box 15)
    - PRE4 Part I - Fostering the Growing Need to Learn: Designs for Continuing Education Manpower (Charters, Alexander N. and Blakely, Robert J.) (unpublished), 1973 (Box 16)
    - PRE5 Part II - A Selected Annotated Bibliography for Continuing Educators for Health Manpower (Charters, Alexander N. and Blakely, Robert J.), 1973 (Box 16)
    - PRE6 Part III - A Report of Some Significant Activities in Continuing Education for Health Manpower n the U.S. (Charters, Alexander N. and Blakely, Robert J.), 1973 (Box 16)
    - PRE7 Part IV - A Critique of Descriptions of Terms in Continuing Education for Health Manpower (Charters, Alexander N. Blakely, and Robert J.), 1973 (Box 16)
    - PRE8 Fostering the Growing Need to Learn (Charters, Alexander N. and Blakely, Robert J.), 1973 (Box 16)
    - PRE9 [MISSING] Newsletter, 1961 (Box 16)
    - PRE10 French Universities and Adult Education, 1962 (Box 16)
    - PRE11 [MISSING] List of Institutions and Individuals Active in University Adult Education, 1965 (Box 16)
  - Papers on Adult Education, University College publications (PUC) (Blue Books)
    - PUC1 Special Report on University College (Charters, Alexander N.), 1955 (Box 16)
    - PUC2 Some Motivational Aspects of College Training (Snygg, Donald), 1956 (Box 16)
    - PUC3 Learning Theory and Its Application to Classroom Teaching (Thelen, Herbert), 1956 (Box 16)
    - PUC4 Learning Theory and Classroom Practice in Adult Education (Getzels, J. W.), 1956 (Box 16)
    - PUC5 Evaluation in Evening colleges (Charters, Alexander N.), 1956 (Box 16)
    - PUC6 Course Construction and the Use of Teaching Resources (Liveright, A. A.), 1957 (Box 16)
    - PUC7 Continuing Education (Crawford, Finla G.), 1958 (Box 16)
    - PUC8 Summary Report on Adult College Students (Knox, Alan B.), 1959 (Box 16)
    - PUC9 Looking Ahead in Adult Education (Tolley, William P.), 1959 (Box 16)
    - PUC10 A Report on the Semester in Italy (Adams, John Clarke), 1960 (Box 16)
    - PUC11 World Affairs Don't Have to be Boring (Cleveland, Harlan), 1960 (Box 16)
    - PUC12 Learning and Change, the Problems of Evaluation in Liberal Adult Education (Powell, John Walker), 1960 (Box 16)
    - PUC13 Government in Action, a Final Report on the Experimental Adult Education Program Presented at University College (Schmidt, Karl M.), 1960 (Box 16)
    - PUC14 Development of an Objective Instrument for Evaluation of Scientific Maturity in Electrical Engineering (Jutila, Sakari Tampani), 1960 (Box 16)
    - PUC15 Local Community Leadership (Freeman, Linton C. et al), 1960 (Box 16)
    - PUC16 The Evening College and Its Relationship to "Community Publics" (Bartlett, Kenneth G.), 1960 (Box 16)
    - PUC17 Bottles Old, Wine New; Wine Old, Bottles New (Schwertman, John B.), 1961 (Box 16)
    - PUC18 The Free University--Its Role in Education for Public Responsibility and the Future of Our Free Society and the Free World (Fletcher, C. Scott), 1961 (Box 16)
    - PUC19 The Story of Sagamore (Applegate, Howard L.), 1961 (Box 16)
    - PUC20 Many Opinions (Diekhoff, John S.), 1961 (Box 16)
    - PUC21 University Adult Education: The Center for Experiment in Education (Liveright, A. A.), 1961 (Box 16)
    - PUC22 We Must be Educator-Administrators (Neville, Howard R.), 1961 (Box 16)
    - PUC23 Adult Education in Australia (Hely, Arnold S. M.), 1961 (Box 16)
    - PUC24 Geographers Look at the World (Cressey, George B. Gould, Peter), 1961 (Box 16)
    - PUC25 The Story of Pinebrook (Applegate, Howard L.), 1962 (Box 16)
    - PUC26 The Story of Minnowbrook (Applegate, Howard L.), 1962 (Box 16)
    - PUC27 Metropolitan Decision-Making: Further Analysis from the Syracuse Study of Local Community Leadership (Freeman, Linton C,), 1962 (Box 16)
    - PUC28 University Adult Education in Some Commonwealth Countries (Raybould, S. G.), 1963 (Box 16)
    - PUC29 The Negro in Syracuse: His Education, Employment, Income and Housing (Campbell, Alan K.), 1964 (Box 16)
    - PUC30 A Kind Word for Mankind (Olson, John F.), 1964 (Box 16)
    - PUC31 The Unfinished Business of Human Rights in Syracuse (Willie, Charles V.), 1965 (Box 16)
    - PUC32 An Investigation of the Status of the Student Personnel Program in Evening Colleges (Simonaitis, John), 1960 (Box 16)
  - Reports series (REP)
    - REP101 New Directions in Programming for University Adult Education (Siegle, Peter E. and Whipple, James B.), 1957 (Box 16)
    - REP102 New Directions in Liberal Education for Executives (Siegle, Peter E.), 1958 (Box 16)
    - REP103 New Directions for Alumni: Continuing Education for the College Graduate (McMahon, Ernest E.), 1960 (Box 16)
    - REP104 New Directions in Degree Programs Especially for Adults (Liveright, A. A. and DeCrow, Roger), 1963 (Box 16)
    - REP105 The Vassar Institute for Women in Business (Vaughan, Marilyn), 1957 (Box 16)
    - REP106 The Changing University (Daigneault, George H., editor), 1959 (Box 16)
    - REP107 University Adult Education in the Arts (Goldman, Freda H.), 1961 (Box 16)
    - REP108 The Audience for Liberal Adult Education (Knox, Alan B.), 1962 (Box 16)
    - REP109 Administrative Practices in University Evening Colleges (DeCrow, Roger), 1962 (Box 16)
    - REP110 Reorientation in Labor Education: A Symposium on Liberal Education for Labor in the University (Goldman, Freda H.), 1962 (Box 16)
    - REP111 Never Too Late for College: The Brooklyn Degree Program for Adults (Stern, Bernard H.), 1963 (Box 16)
    - REP112 Research Arrangements Within University Adult Education Divisions (Knox, A. B.), 1963 (Box 16)
    - REP113 A Conspectus to the Self-Study Project of University College, the University of Chicago (Roth, Robert M., editor), 1964 (Box 16)
    - REP114 Metroplex Assembly: An Experiment in Community Education (Johnson, Eugene I.), 1965 (Box 16)
    - REP115 Bachelor of Liberal Studies: Development of a Curriculum at the University of Oklahoma (Burkett, J. E. Riggiers, Paul C.) (Box 16)
    - REP116 Creativity Research and Its Implications for Adult Education (Zahn, Jane C.), 1966 (Box 16)
    - REP117 The Arts in Higher Adult Education: A Second Review of Programs (Goldman, Freda H.), 1967 (Box 16)
    - REP118 Changing Patterns in Continuing Education for Business (Olean, Sally J.), 1967 (Box 16)
    - REP119 Listening Groups: Mass Media in Adult Education (Ohliger, John), 1967 (Box 16)
    - REP120 Adult Education and Adult Needs (Havighurst, Robert J. and Orr, Betty), 1960 (Box 16)
    - REP121 Forms and Forces in University Adult Education (Carey, James T.), 1961 (Box 16)
    - REP122 A Comparison of the Effectiveness of Residential and Nonresidential Learning Situations (Lacognata, A. A.), 1961 (Box 16)
    - REP123 The Development of the University Evening College as Observed in Ten Urban Universities (Carey, James T.), 1961 (Box 16)
    - REP124 New Perspectives in University Correspondence Study (Wedemeyer, Charles and Childs, Gayle B)., 1961 (Box 16)
    - REP125 Evaluating Liberal Adult Education (Miller, Harry L. and McGuire, Christine H.), 1961 (Box 16)
    - REP126 Decision Making in the University Evening College (Daigneault, George H.), 1963 (Box 16)
    - REP127 Teaching Styles and Learning (Solomon, Daniel and Rosenberg, Larry Bexdek, William), 1963 (Box 16)
    - REP128 The Continuing Learner (Solomon, Daniel, editor), 1964 (Box 16)
    - REP129 The Exeter Papers: Report of the First International Conference on the Comparative Study of Adult Education (Liveright, A. A. and Haygood, Norwood), 1968 (Box 16)
    - REP130 A Study of Adult Education in the United States (Liveright, A. A.), 1968 (Box 16)
    - REP131 Ivory Towers in the Market Place (Dyer, John P.), 1956 (Box 16)
    - REP132 The Part-time College Teacher (Gowin, D. B. and Daigneault, George H.), 1961 (Box 16)
    - REP133 Ability and Achievement of Evening College and Extension Students (DeCrow, Roger), 1959 (Box 16)
    - REP134 Why Students Drop Out: A Study of Evening College Student Motivations (Carey, James T.), 1953 (Box 16)
    - REP135 Cumulative Indexes to the Association of University Evening Colleges Proceedings and National University Extension Association Proceedings, 1915-1957 (Box 16)
    - REP136 The Role of Liberal Arts in the University Evening College Curriculum, Pinebrook, N. Y., October 1954 (CSLEA Conference Report) (Box 16)
    - REP137 Tradition and Innovation in University Adult Education, Swampscott, Massachusetts, October1954 (CSLEA Conference Report) (Box 16)
    - REP138 The University's Responsibility for the General Education of Adults, Chicago, Illinois, March 3-5, 1956(CSLEA Conference Report) (Box 16)
    - REP139 The Concerns of the Dean in University Adult Education, Chicago, Illinois, March 5-7, 1956 (CSLEA Conference Report) (Box 16)
    - REP140 A Report: Administrative Policies and Practices of Evening Colleges (Neuffer, Frank R) (Box 16)
    - REP141 A Report: A Review of Center Activities and Projects (CSLEA), 1956 (Box 16)
    - REP142 A Report: A Review of Center Activities and Projects (CSLEA), 1957; 1956 (Box 16)
    - REP143 A Report: A Review of Future Directions of the Center and A Report of Current Activities (CSLEA), 1958 (Box 16)
    - REP144 CSLEA in Retrospect (Liveright, A. A.), 1968 (Box 16)
  - Reprints series (RPR)
    - RPR1 "The Evening College." Houle, Cyril O. Journal of Higher Education Vol. XXV, No. 7, Oct. 1954 (Box 16)
    - RPR2 "The University's Role in Adult Education: A Journal Symposium." (Diekhoff, John S.; Leys, Wayne A. R.; Conley, William H.; Schwertman, John B. Journal of Higher Education Vol. XXVI, No. 1, Jan. 1955 (Box 16)
    - RPR3 "The American University and Adult Education." Houle, Cyril O. Educational Record, Oct. 1955 (Box 16)
    - RPR4 "Liberal Education Reexamined" Horn, Francis H. Harvard Educational Review, Vol. XXVI, No. 4, Fall 1956 (Box 16)
    - RPR5 "What's Your Line? The Task of the Adult Educator" Miller, Harry L. Adult Leadership, Vol. 6, No. 3, Sept. 1957 (Box 16)
    - RPR6 "The Alumni University." Diekhoff, John S. Journal of Higher Education, Vol. XXVIII, No. 7, Oct. 1957 (Box 16)
    - RPR7 "AUEX Background - From Coffee to Capers to Educational Leadership." Love, Robert A. AUEC Newsletter, Vol. VI, No. 1, Nov. 1957 (Box 16)
    - RPR8 "An Exchange of Letters Between Alfred [Albert] Einstein and Sigmund Freud on the Subject Why War?" (Box 16)
    - RPR9 "Why Don't We Have Better Teaching for Adults?" Miller, Harry L., 1957 (Box 16)
  - Syracuse University Related publications (SUR)
    - SUR1 To Serve the Public Interest: Educational Broadcasting in the United States (Blakely, Robert J.), 1979 (Box 17)
    - SUR2 Comparing Adult Education Worldwide (Charters, Alexander N. et al.), 1981; hardcover; published by Jossey Bass (Box 17)
    - SUR3 Changing Approaches to Studying Adult Education (Long, Huey B. and Hiemstra, Roger), 1980 (Box 17)
    - SUR4 Information Resources for Educators of Adults (Charters, Alexander N.), 1979 (Box 17)
    - SUR5 CAEO Through the Years (Charters, Alexander N.), 1977 (Box 17)
    - SUR6 [MISSING] The Teaching Profession and the Education of Adults: A Review and an Agenda (Committee on Adult Education World Confederation of Organizations of the Teaching Profession) (Box 17)
    - SUR7 A Statement on Coalition of Adult Education Organizations (Charters, Alexander N.), 1976 (Box 17)
  - William Pearson Tolley Medal series (WPT)
    - WPT1 The Uncommon School (Houle, Cyril O.), 1966 (Box 17)
    - WPT2 University and The Community (Mehta, Mohan S.), 1969 (Box 17)